A Guide to the Noel Behn papers M1084
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- CLIPPINGS AND MAGAZINES
  - Copies of "The New Yorker," "Vanity Fair," "Esquire," "Playbill," "Time," "Script Magazine," "Venezuela," "New West," etc., miscellaneous clippings, photocopies of clippings, tear sheets, etc.; "Homicide" reviews, clippings regarding Lindbergh case, news clips from Russia. Mostly 1980s-1990s. (Box 152)
  - "Playbill" and other artistic publications, "Boston," "New York Magazine," "Memories," "Consumer Reports," clippings and photocopies of clippings regarding Soviet Union, Lindbergh case, Nosovitsky, etc.; miscellaneous publicity materials. 1970s-1980s, miscellaneous dates. (Box 168)
  - "Playbill," "Stagebill," "Gamut," and other artistic publications, clippings, photocopies of clippings, articles, tear sheets. (Box 186)